foreign [Music]
congratulations for having completed this part of the Preparatory steps of inner engineering
now the next step is the transmission of the powerful shambhavi mahamudra
it's best that you prepare your body and your mind and your emotion and your energy system
to be ready for this preparing your body preparing your mind and Energies
so that you should perceive this you should receive this well because this
is an experiential aspect this is not intellectual in nature for millions of people across the world
becomes a turning point in their life
that is in many ways the trajectory of
Life can change simply because of this
simple powerful process it's my wish and my blessing it should be so for you also [Music]
Maha mudra practitioner for about 12 years now over the years you know as as life progresses
there are things challenges um emotional career professional Etc that you come
through I think the key benefit that I have noticed is that it lets me keep an even keel
uh it doesn't matter what I'm going through on the outside I'm able to stay happy I'm able to
maintain my sense of humor and that's the key thing it's helped me stay even keeled through
a lot of ups and downs I actually think it allows you a great deal of very almost cool
focus when you need it it just means you're able to recognize a situation and what it requires
in 2018 I enrolled for the inner engineering program got initiated into shambhavi mamudra
the shambhavi kriya is instilled disciplined in me as far as I think anxiety is concerned I
remember before the career when I had bad work days I did a lot of anxiety eating
and um a lot of tension after I did in our engineering it is allowed me to maintain my
calm and my composure and lost a lot of weight I have been eating well I have been sleeping well
and I have been handling situations in a much much better way people who know me tell me that
I've changed a lot for good which is which is a compliment for me especially I feel like walking
into this I wanted to just come out of it as a more conscious person in life and being able to
stay in a happy State and I feel like walking out of this I've come out with so much more I
feel like I've been coming out of it as not so caught up in anything that's not now [Music]